

FRONT-END DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

chvndler.ch@icloud.com www.chvndler.ch/ 336-244-8939

Introduction

Driven Creative Director and Multimedia Designer with demonstrated experience leading $creative \ teams \ and \ design \ projects. \ Proven \ strengths \ in \ Film \ Production, \ Motion/Graphic$ design, and Web design. Proficient in a variety of web technologies, frameworks, and software languages (React.js, Next.js, Typescript, Node.js). Focused arts and design professional with a Bachelor's degree, in Sports Medicine and a minor in New Media and Design from The University of North Carolina at Greensboro.

Creative Stack



Experience

Lead Creative Director - ISI® Elite Training

NOVEMBER 2018 - NOVEMBER 2022

Directed creative teams on several design projects and national marketing campaigns within the Health and Wellness industry. Obtained a vast amount of business knowledge and played a key role in franchise growth.

- · Succeeded in executing a clear brand identity and direction
- · Delivered design systems, guidelines, and brand standards
- · Developed the brand image and defined a clear brand voice
- · Produced all video assets and advertising media
- Prepared all brand logos, and artwork
- · Designed, developed, and maintained several web apps and domains
- · Email campaign design
- Built professional relationships with franchise partners and owners
- · Made critical technology decisions to scale · Integrated CRM's, API's, and various marketing automations
- · Technology partners include: MindBody®, MarianTek®, Zapier®, ADP®, Vercel & others

Video/Film Team Intern - Elevation Church

SEPTEMBER 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018

Worked closely with the well-known Elevation Worship team as a film intern. Collaborated with creative teams on numerous films, music videos, and motion design projects.

- · Visual tour elements for Elevation Worship
- · Music video editing
- · Short film/Documentary editing

Owner & Director - ATLR® Design

MAY 2020 - PRESENT

 $\mathbf{ATLR} \textbf{@} \text{ is an ever-expanding library of design components} ^{\text{\tiny{TM}}}$

My goal with this project is to continuously provide simple & performant design assets, components, and resources to designers like myself, without following trends and industry noise.

- · React UI Components
- · Graphic Textures, Assets, Plug-ins and more
- Icon Libraries
- · Color Systems
- · Starter Projects
- · Adobe® Extensions, Plugins, and Panels

Production Team - UNCG® Athletics

Worked alongside a team to produce live broadcasting experiences for all athletic teams at The University of North Carolina at Greensboro.

- · Technical Directed (TD) live video productions
- · Audio engineering
- Produced for ESPN3 for larger televised match-ups
- · Lead Camera Operator
- · Replay System Operator
- · Broadcast Graphics Operator

Education

The University of North Carolina at Greensboro

2013 - 2017, GREENSBORO, NORTH CAROLINA

Bachelor's degree, in Sports Medicine Minoring in New Media and Design

9+ Years of Design Experience

~ 2013 - PRESENT

Multidisciplinary designer. Self taught.

- Software Developing (React, Typescript, Next.js, css, js, Node.js)
 UI Design (Figma, CSS-inJS, Styled Components)
- Video editing & film production (Premiere Pro, After Effects)
- Graphic Design (Photoshop, Figma, XD, Affinity 2)
- Motion Design (After Effects)
- 3d Modeling (Blender, Unity)

Highlights

NCAA Division I Athlete - Men's Soccer

The University of North Carolina at Greensboro

2013 - 2017, GREENSBORO, NORTH CAROLINA

Southern Conference (SoCon)

U.S. Soccer Development Academy

NC Fusion Academy (Greensboro, North Carolina) U16 - U18 Boy's Soccer Player

Olympic Development Program ODP

U.S. Youth Soccer Olympic Development Program Player for South Region ODP

CONNECT

@chvndlerch @chvndler

@chvndler.eth @chvndler.eth

@chandler

@chv.ndler

CDC